depedclick.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - DepedClick

At DepEd Click, accessible from <https://www.depedclick.com/>, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by DepEd Click and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at depedclick@gmail.com

DepEd Click follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

Privacy Policies

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on DepEd Click, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that DepEd Click has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

DepEd Click does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in DepEd Click. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
